Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Records SC0112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Director's Office, Series 2
  - Directors' Office records, 1965-1993; Accession ARCH-2011-171
    - Fundraising, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Goals and objectives, 1979-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Three Year Plan, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Meyer Library--history, reports, mission, goals and objectives, 1964-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Near West Campus, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - News clippings, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Organization charts, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Preservation of library materials, 1978-1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Program renewal document, 1987 Apr 22 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Provost's Task Force on Library Planning for the Future, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Three year vision statements, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Recruitment of librarians, 1990 Feb (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Redesigning the Acquisitions-to-Access Process, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Regional Planning-Campus-Wide, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Stanford University Library Associates, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Systems/Socrates (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Administrative Services, Series 3
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Budget Summary, 1979-1980 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Stanford/Berkeley, Sloan/Mellon BALLOTS (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Unrestricted Current Fund (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Resources Development (Coll. Development) (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Lib. Preservation (Binding & Finishing) (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Technical Services Information (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Science Branches (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Bender Room (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Automation Division (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Unviersity Libraries Book Acquisition Funds (Named) (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Book Funds (Named Funds) (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Bio Sci Book Funds (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - University Archives (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Branch Libraries Book Funds (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Ballots Budget (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Admin. Svcs. Annual Report (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - 190-81 Budget (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Budget Coding Revision (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Chron Files (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - Word Processing (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - Telephones (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - Work Simplification (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - Systems Librarian (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - Systems Training File (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - Unviersity Automated Budget System Poposal (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - Departmental Budget Requests, 1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 26B)
  - Research Libraries Group, 1981 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Research Libraries Group, 1979-1980 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Technical Services, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Tanner Funds (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Gift Funds - Book & non-Book (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Buck Estate Funds (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Bonsall Funds (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - SUL Annual Statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Mail & Messenger & Supply Services (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Mail/Messenger & Supply Services (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Procurement (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Photocopy Service (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Word Processing Unit (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Accounting - Indirect Costs (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Graphics (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Automated Budget (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Safety & Security (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Insurance/Risk Management (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Risk Management-Valuation of the Library Collection (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Risk Management-Valuation of the Library Collection - Draft (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Library Cabinet, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Branch Libraries, 1981 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - Meyer Catalog (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Public Services, 1979-1982 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Technical Services, 1981 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - Future of the Catalog - draft (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Library User Survey, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Academic Planning Office Report, 1978-1979 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Academic Planning Office Report, 1979-1980 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Budget Letter, 1981-1982 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Budget Letter, 1981-1982 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1980 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, 1971-1975 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - SUL Cost Study, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - BALLOTS - Budget Background, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - BALLOTS - Budget Background, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - BALLOTS - Budget, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - BALLOTS - Budget, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - BALLOTS - SPIRES, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - BALLOTS - SPIRES, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - BAP (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1971-1975 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1971-1975 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1971-1975 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1971-1977 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1971-1977 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Budget Letter, 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Budget Letter, Book Matls. Documentation, 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Budget Letter, 1980-1981 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Budget Recommendation, 1981-1982 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Printed Budget (Box 154, Folder 16)
- Technical Services, Series 4
  - Catalog Department
    - Automation committee, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Automation committee, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Library automation files, 1984-1987; Accession ARCH-1999-328
  - BALLOTS, Accession ARCH.2014-062
    - 2 VHS cassettes, photographic slides, and user manuals (Box 1)
  - Socrates Advisory Group records, Accession ARCH-1997-250
  - Cath Tierney, AUL for Technical Services, records, 1994-2014; Accession ARCH-2015-024
    - Diroff Notebook 1, 1994 Sep. 29-1995 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Notebook 2, 1995 Mar. 8-1994 Oct. 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Notebook 4, 1995 Nov. 1-1996 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Notebook 5, 1996 May 7-1996 Dec. 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Notebook 6, 1996 Dec. 13-1997 Jun. 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Notebook 7, 1997 Jun. 5-1998 Nov. 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Notebook 8, 1997 Nov. 10-1998 Apr. 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Notebook 9, 1998 Apr. 6-1998 Nov. 29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Notebook 10, 1998 Sep. 29-1999 Mar. 24 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Notebook 11, 1999 Mar. 25-1999 Sep. 28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Notebook 12, 2000 Sep. 29-2000 Feb. 25 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Notebook 13, 2000 Feb. 23-2000 Sep. 21 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Notebook 14, 2000 Sep. 21 - 2001 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Notebook 15, 2001 May 27-2001 Jul. 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Notebook 16, 2001 Jul. 12-2001 Dec. 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Notebook 17, 2001 Dec. 4-2002 Apr. 15 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Notebook 18, 2002 Apr. 17-2002 Oct. 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Notebook 19, 2002 Oct.-2002 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Notebook 20, 2002 Nov.-2002 Feb. 20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Notebook 21, 2003 Feb. 21-2003 Jul. 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Notebook 22, 2003 Jul. 2-2003 Nov. 25 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Notebook 23, 2003 Nov. 25-2004 Apr. 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Notebook 24, 2004 Apr. 6-2004 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Notebook 25, 2004 Oct. 5-2005 Jan. 26 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Notebook 26, 2005 Jan. 27-2005 Jun. 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Notebook 27, 2005 Jun. 20-2005 Oct. 27 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Notebook 28, 2005 Oct. 26-2006 Feb. 21 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Notebook 29, 2006 Feb. 22-2006 Jun. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Notebook 30, 2006 Jun. 13-2006 Oct. 6 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Notebook 31, 2006 Oct. 16-2007 Feb. 28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Notebook 32, 2007 Feb. 28-2007 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Notebook 33, 2007 May 31-2007 Aug. 27 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Notebook 34, 2007 Aug. 23-2007 Dec. 18 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Notebook 35, 2007 Dec. 19-2008 Apr. 30 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Notebook 36, 2008 May 1-2008 Sep. 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Notebook 37, 2008 Oct. 10-2009 Feb. 4 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Notebook 38, 0 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Notebook 39, 2009 May 18-2009 Nov. 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Notebook 40, 2009 Nov. 3- 2010 Apr. 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Notebook 41, 2010 Apr. 7-2010 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Notebook 42, 2010 Aug. 31-2011 July 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Notebook 43, 2011 Feb. 3-2011 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Notebook 44, 2011 June 15-2011 Nov. 30 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Notebook 45, 2011 Dec. 1-2012 Feb. 8 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Notebook 46, 2012 May 10-2012 Nov. 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Notebook 47, 2012 Nov. 13-2013 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Notebook 48, 2013 May 6-2013 Nov. 26 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Notebook 49, 2013 Dec. 2-2014 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Notebook 50, 2014 May 20-2014 Oct. 29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - TS Building (Prelim), 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - TS BLDG. Proposal, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Library Technical Services Building, 1998 Apr. 14 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - TS BLDG., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Coutts Library Services Inc. Reponse, 2005 May 24 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Coutts Library Services Inc. Reponse, 38792 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - OCLC Pricing & Costs, 1995-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Special Projects Funding, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Special Projects Funding, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - LANE/GSB Vendor Selection, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Cataloo Dept., 1995-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pres/Provost Funds, 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Preservation, 1994-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - EEMs-Mellon, 40512 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Year 2000, 1998 Oct. 25-1998 Nov. 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - SFX link server, 2004 Sept. 30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ordering Services, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - WEST: Agreement & Background, 2011 Apr. 4-2014 Sept. 5 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - WEST: Disclosure & OCLC Pilot, 2011 Dec. 16-2012 June 7 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - WEST: Planning Grant, 2004 May 6-2010 Dec. 13 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - TS Reengineering, 1994 Oct. 5-1995 Jan. 26 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - TS Reengineering - Staff Planning, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - TS Reengineering, Vol I, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - TS Reengineering, Vol II, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - TS Reengineering, Vol III, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Google Big Picture, 40729 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Google Collections, 2004 June 7-2009 Feb. 18 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Google Copyright, 2005 Feb. 7-2007 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Google Contract Logo, 2005 Apr. 14-2010 Oct. 27 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Google Grin, 2005 Aug. 30-2014 May 6 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Google Hosted Solution, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Google Image Quality, 2005 May 24-2005 July 29 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Google - Local Misc., 2005 Sept. 16-2010 Oct. 27 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Google Meeting w/ Google, 2005 Mar. 11-2010 Oct. 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Google Metadata, 2005 June 20-2010 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Google - Non consumptive research, 2009 Oct. 20 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Google Synchronization, 2005 Apr.-2007 May 30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Google Partners, 2004 Dec. 17-2011 Feb. 13 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Google Presentations, 2005 June 16-2012 Sept. 26 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Google Preservation, 2005 June 17-2009 Apr. 7 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Google Process, 2004 June 28-2011 July 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Google PR, 2004 Dec. 15-2010 Mar. 9 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Google Returned Content, 2005 Jan. 20-2012 Mar. 9 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Google Rollback, 2011 Sept. 19-2012 July 5 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Google SAL3 to Google, 2007 May 11-2010 Jan. 14 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Google Stats/Costs, 2004 July 7-2008 Apr. 28 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Google Staffing, 2006 June 30-2008 Apr. 10 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Google Settlement, 2008 Oct. 2-2013 Nov. 14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Collection Development, Series 5
- Human Resources, Series 6
- Public Services, Series 7
- Gifts and Exchanges, Series 8
- Special Collections, Series 9
  - University Archives-Ralph Hansen talks (Box 159)
- Cataloging
  - Automation Committee, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Automation Committee, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Arrears Reports, 1968 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Arrears Reports, 1969 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Arrears Reports, 1970 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Arrears Reports, 1971 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Arrears Reports, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Arrears Reports, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Arrears Reports, 1974 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Arrears Reports, 1975 (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - Arrears Reports, 1976 (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - Ballots, 1969 (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Ballots, 1970 (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Ballots, 1971 (Box 241, Folder 12)
  - Ballots, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 13)
  - Ballots, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 14)
  - Ballots, 1974 (Box 241, Folder 15)
  - Building Services, 1974-1978 (Box 241, Folder 16)
  - Building Services, 1979-1982 (Box 241, Folder 17)
  - Equipments Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 241, Folder 18)
  - Equipments Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 241, Folder 19)
  - Equipments Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 241, Folder 20)
  - Equipments Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 241, Folder 21)
  - Equipments Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 241, Folder 22)
  - Archive of Recorded Sound, circa 1970 (Box 241, Folder 23)
  - Meyer Cataloging, 1963-1968 (Box 241, Folder 24)
  - Meyer Cataloging, 1969-1974 (Box 241, Folder 25)
  - Flu Shots, 1974-1975 (Box 241, Folder 26)
  - Monthly Supply Expendit., 1982-1983 (Box 241, Folder 27)
  - Completed photocopy requests, 1983-? (Box 241, Folder 28)
  - Completed photocopy requests, 1984-? (Box 241, Folder 29)
  - Centrex Expenditures, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 30)
  - CIT Accounts, 1983-1984 (Box 241, Folder 31)
  - Supply Requests, 1983-1984 (Box 241, Folder 32)
  - Supply Requests, 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1957-1958/1965-1966 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Narrative Summary, 1971-1972 (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1972/1973-1974 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Production Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 242, Folder 15)
  - SUL Cost Study, 1971 (Box 242, Folder 16)
  - SUL Cost Study, 1971 (Box 242, Folder 17)
  - Ballots Statistics, 1975 (Box 242, Folder 18)
  - Time Analysis, 1970-1971 (Box 242, Folder 19)
  - Time Analysis, 1975 (Box 242, Folder 20)
  - Cat. & Assist. Time study, 1976/1977 (Box 242, Folder 21)
  - Debbie J. Adams (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Jennifer Armstrong (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Andrea Marianna Bahmann (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Slyvia Baiman (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Baskeyy (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Miranoa Beaven (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Linda Sue Bendt (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Denise D. Bedford (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - Karen Bendorf (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Diana M. Blakely (Box 243, Folder 10)
  - Judy Blount (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - Ralph Bogert (Box 243, Folder 12)
  - Donna Bolster (Box 243, Folder 13)
  - Garret Bowles (Box 243, Folder 14)
  - Arlene M. Breuiten (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - Sally Buchanan (Box 243, Folder 16)
  - Pricila L. Calvo (Box 243, Folder 17)
  - Heather Campbell (Box 243, Folder 18)
  - Catherine M. Carroll (Box 243, Folder 19)
  - Dianne S. Claerbout (Box 243, Folder 20)
  - Katherine Condon (Box 243, Folder 21)
  - Pat Coxon (Box 243, Folder 22)
  - Jeanna A. Darbinian (Box 243, Folder 23)
  - Glen Denny (Box 243, Folder 24)
  - Ben Dickinson (Box 243, Folder 25)
  - Sarah Donnelly (Box 243, Folder 26)
  - Helen Drummon (Box 243, Folder 27)
  - Yvonne Dvorak (Box 243, Folder 28)
  - Susan K. Ebbers (Box 243, Folder 29)
  - Terence Egan (Box 243, Folder 30)
  - George R. Esenwern (Box 243, Folder 31)
  - Marcia Fentress (Box 243, Folder 32)
  - Emil Bababli (Box 243, Folder 33)
  - David Goetxman (Box 243, Folder 34)
  - Helen Hahn-Steichen (Box 243, Folder 35)
  - Jay Hahn-Steichn (Box 243, Folder 36)
  - Cheryl Hall (Box 243, Folder 37)
  - Ralph Hansen (Box 243, Folder 38)
  - Evelyn Hanson (Box 243, Folder 39)
  - Diane Harris (Box 243, Folder 40)
  - Judith Holley (Box 243, Folder 41)
  - Jeanette Horley (Box 243, Folder 42)
  - Roland Hutchinson (Box 243, Folder 43)
  - Maria Iglesias (Box 243, Folder 44)
  - Jeffrey T. Kane (Box 243, Folder 45)
  - Jean Kao (Box 243, Folder 46)
  - Constance B. Keffer (Box 243, Folder 47)
  - Kaiko Kukuchi (Box 243, Folder 48)
  - Joseph Kladko (Box 243, Folder 49)
  - Leroy Kromm (Box 243, Folder 50)
  - Lawrence E. Leonard (Box 243, Folder 51)
  - Janell Levy (Box 243, Folder 52)
  - Susana Liu (Box 243, Folder 53)
  - Ralph Lyon, Jr. (Box 243, Folder 54)
  - Charlotte Mercado (Box 243, Folder 55)
  - Judith J. Merrihue (Box 243, Folder 56)
  - Virginia Mesa (Box 243, Folder 57)
  - Jozsef Miklosvary (Box 243, Folder 58)
  - Joan Miles (Box 243, Folder 59)
  - Andy Miller (Box 243, Folder 60)
  - Paul Mosher (Box 243, Folder 61)
  - Jim Meyers (Box 243, Folder 62)
  - Yvonne Myers (Box 243, Folder 63)
  - Susan Anderes (Box 243, Folder 64)
  - David Bade (Box 243, Folder 65)
  - Ila Doshit (Box 243, Folder 66)
  - Maria Leal (Box 243, Folder 67)
  - Claudia Rowley (Box 243, Folder 68)
  - Greg Smith (Box 243, Folder 69)
  - Gladys Starr (Box 243, Folder 70)
  - AACR, 1968-1987 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - AACR II Implementation, 1980-1983 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Abbreviated Cataloging, 1981 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Absence Reporting, 1971-1981 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council Com. On Univ. Libraries, 1970-1981 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Acquisition Council Minutes, 1970-1976 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Acquisitions/Catalog Meetings, 1970-1975 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Acquisitions Department, 1970-1981 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Acquisitions Dept. - Book Selection, 1971-1982 (Box 250, Folder 9)
  - ACRL, 1979 (Box 250, Folder 10)
  - Added Copies, 1963-1981 (Box 250, Folder 11)
  - Added Copy Manual, 1963-1972 (Box 250, Folder 12)
  - Added Copies/Added Volumes Unit, 1979-1980 (Box 250, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Engineering Project, 1972 (Box 250, Folder 14)
  - Classics Projects, 1976-1980 (Box 250, Folder 15)
  - Music Fast Cat. Project, 1974-1975 (Box 250, Folder 16)
  - Psychology Project, 1973 (Box 250, Folder 17)
  - Shelf List Project, 1973 (Box 250, Folder 18)
  - Torn Card Project, 1972-1979 (Box 250, Folder 19)
  - Added Volumes, 1977 (Box 250, Folder 20)
  - Administrative/Advisory Groups, 1973-1975 (Box 250, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 250, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Forum, 1979-1981 (Box 250, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Services Office, 1976-1980 (Box 250, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Support Group, 1976-1980 (Box 250, Folder 25)
  - Affirmative Action, 1970-1980 (Box 250, Folder 26)
  - ALA, 1981 (Box 250, Folder 27)
  - ALA, 1979-1980 (Box 250, Folder 28)
  - Analytics, 1963-1981 (Box 250, Folder 29)
  - Analytics - Serial, 1970-1981 (Box 250, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1980-1981 (Box 250, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1979-1980 (Box 250, Folder 32)
  - Catalog Department Annual Report, 1978/1979 (Box 250, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report: Catalog Dept., 1977-1978 (Box 250, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1976-1977 (Box 250, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1975-1976 (Box 250, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1974-1975 (Box 250, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1973-1974 (Box 250, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1972-1973 (Box 250, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1971-1972 (Box 250, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1970-1971 (Box 250, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1969-1970 (Box 250, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1968-1969 (Box 250, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report: Catalog, 1967-1968 (Box 250, Folder 44)
  - Annual Reports: Acquisitions Dept., 1979-1981 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports: Conservation Office, 1973-1974 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports: Serial Dept., 1977-1981 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports: SUL, 1968-1972 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports: Systems Office, 1980-1981 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Archive of Recorded Sound, 1980-1982 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - ARL, 1971-1982 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Arrears Memos, 1979-1982 (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - Arrears Report - Final Report and Support Documents, 28825 (Box 251, Folder 9)
  - Arrears Report - Final Report and Support Documents, 28642 (Box 251, Folder 10)
  - Art Cataloging, 1967-1977 (Box 251, Folder 11)
  - Aet Library, 1969-1980 (Box 251, Folder 12)
  - Associated Audio Archives Project, 1979-1982 (Box 251, Folder 13)
  - Audio/Visual Cataloging, 1969-1982 (Box 251, Folder 14)
  - Auditing Classes, 1969-1976 (Box 251, Folder 15)
  - Authorities amp; Cross References Manual - Memos, Drafts, Revisions, 1970-1981 (Box 251, Folder 16)
  - Authority Files, 1968-1981 (Box 251, Folder 17)
  - Authority Records, 1973-1981 (Box 251, Folder 18)
  - Automated Circulation System - Specs., 1980-1981 (Box 251, Folder 19)
  - Automation, 1977-1981 (Box 251, Folder 20)
  - Auxiliary Collections, 1965-1975 (Box 251, Folder 21)
  - Ballots Catalog Cards, 1969-1979 (Box 251, Folder 22)
  - Ballots/Cataloging Standards, 1974-1978 (Box 251, Folder 23)
  - Ballots Change Requests, 1972-1978 (Box 251, Folder 24)
  - Ballots Costs, 1971-1979 (Box 251, Folder 25)
  - Ballots Decision Manual, 1978 (Box 251, Folder 26)
  - Ballots Documentation, 1975-1978 (Box 251, Folder 27)
  - Ballots Management Seminar, 1974 (Box 251, Folder 28)
  - Ballots Monthly Reports, 1970-1079 (Box 251, Folder 29)
  - Ballots - Network File Design, 1978 (Box 251, Folder 30)
  - Ballots Newsletter, 1977 (Box 251, Folder 31)
  - Ballots Offset Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 251, Folder 32)
  - Ballots Public Services, 1976-1979 (Box 251, Folder 33)
  - Ballots Rates, 1976-1979 (Box 251, Folder 34)
  - Ballots: Sprint, 1978-1979 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Ballots: Terminals, 1972-1979 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Ballots Training, 1972-1979 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Ballots Trouble Logs, 1972-1978 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Ballots Users Group, 1973-1979 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Ballots User's Workshop, 28383 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Benefits, 1974-1981 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographic Center, Technical Serv., 1971-981 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographic Description amp; Control, 1975-1981 (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - Bibliographic Instruction, 1977-1981 (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - Bibliographical Notes, 1977-1981 (Box 252, Folder 11)
  - Bibtech, 1980-1981 (Box 252, Folder 12)
  - Binding and Finishing, 1970-1983 (Box 252, Folder 13)
  - Book Cards, 1973-1975 (Box 252, Folder 14)
  - Book catalog - Economics, 1964 (Box 252, Folder 15)
  - Book Trucks, 1979-1980 (Box 252, Folder 16)
  - Bookstore Purchases, 1977-1979 (Box 252, Folder 17)
  - Branch Libraries, 1972-1980 (Box 252, Folder 18)
  - Branner Earth Sciences Library, 1969-1981 (Box 252, Folder 19)
  - Briggs Memorial Library, 1972-1974 (Box 252, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 252, Folder 21)